<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecycleView</string>
    <string name="news_content">
    By Press Trust of India: Vice-President and Rajya Sabha Chairman Jagdeep Dhankhar on Thursday attacked Congress leader Rahul Gandhi for his comments regarding microphones being turned off in Parliament, and said he would be on the "wrong side" of the Constitution if he stayed silent on the issue.
    Speaking at an event to launch veteran Congress leader and former parliamentarian Karan Singhs book on the Mundaka Upanishad, Dhankhar spoke extensively on the former Congress presidents remarks made in London.Amid an acrimonious exchange between the Congress and the BJP over Rahul Gandhis statements in London, Nagaland minister Temjen Imna Along commented on a post made by the official handle of the CongressStand up for what you believe in, even if it means you stand alone the post with a photo of Rahul Gandhi says. In the photo, Rahul Gandhi can be seen in a suit with his hands in the pockets, posing for the photo as he attended an interactive session at the Chatham House in London.Nagaland BJP chiAlong commented on the photo: "One has to accept that the photo is nice. Confidence and pose are next level." On social media, Temjen is known for his witty comments. As the BJP leader remarked about Rahul Gandhi and there was nothing scornful in it, it was an amusing moment for many social media users. Later,the minister made another post implying that the caption with the photo was not original.
    The Congress has hit out at Vice President Jagdeep Dhankhar for his criticism of Rahul Gandhi\' remarks in the UK, saying that the Rajya Sabha chairman is an umpire and cannot be a cheerleader for any ruling dispensation.The Congress\' reaction came after Vice President and Rajya Sabha Chairman Dhankhar attacked Gandhi for his comments regarding microphones being turned off in Parliament, and said he would be on the "wrong side" of the Constitution if he stayed silent on the issue.

</string>
</resources>
